<odoo>
    <data>
        <record id="medicine_1" model="patient.medicals">
        	<field name = "name">ZYRTEC</field>
        	<field name = "description">Relieves your worst allergy symptoms, indoors and out.</field>
        </record>

        <record id="medicine_2" model="patient.medicals">
        	<field name = "name">Aspirin</field>
        	<field name = "description">Aspirin, or acetylsalicylic acid (ASA), is commonly used as a pain reliever for minor aches and pains and to reduce fever. It is also an anti-inflammatory drug and can be used as a blood thinner.</field>
        </record>


        <record id="medicine_3" model="patient.medicals">
        	<field name = "name">Augmentin</field>
        	<field name = "description">Augmentin contains a combination of amoxicillin and clavulanate potassium. Amoxicillin is an antibiotic belonging to a group of drugs called penicillins. Amoxicillin fights bacteria in the body.

			Clavulanate potassium is a beta-lactamase inhibitor that helps prevent certain bacteria from becoming resistant to amoxicillin.

			Augmentin is used to treat many different infections caused by bacteria, such as sinusitis, pneumonia, ear infections, bronchitis, urinary tract infections, and infections of the skin.</field>
        	<field name = "scientific_name"> amoxicillin and clavulanate potassium</field>
			<field name = "titer_ids" eval="[(6,0,[ref('medical_center_managment.titer_2'),ref('medical_center_managment.titer_3'),ref('medical_center_managment.titer_4')])]"/>
        </record>

        <record id="medicine_4" model="patient.medicals">
        	<field name = "name">Aspicot</field>
        	<field name = "description">Aspicot is an antiplatelet drug which is used to prevent clots in blood vessels and also relieves pain and inflammation. It can be taken in combination with other antiplatelets for a better action. It is not recommended in patients with bleeding disorders. Close monitoring of platelets count is necessary.</field>
        	<field name = "titer_ids" eval="[ref('medical_center_managment.titer_1')]"/>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo> 